Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[Reborn from the Ashes]
[ولدت من الرماد]
[Episode 3]
[الحلقة 3]
The Su Family refused to marry their daughter
رفضت عائلة سو تزويج ابنتهم
to the sickly son of the Prince's Mansion,
إلى الابن المريض لقصر الأمير،
so,
لذا،
they planned to have Zhijin marry
لقد خططوا لزواج تشيجين
in her place.
في مكانها.
But now,
ولكن الآن،
she is dead at my place.
لقد ماتت في مكاني.
How can I explain this?
كيف يمكنني أن أشرح هذا؟
If I marry into the Wanyan Family
إذا تزوجت من عائلة وانيان
as the eldest daughter of the Su Family,
باعتبارها الابنة الكبرى لعائلة سو،
I can search in the mansion for proof that my father was wronged.
أستطيع أن أبحث في القصر عن دليل على أن والدي قد تعرض للظلم.
Madam Yun, don't worry so much.
السيدة يون، لا تقلقي كثيرًا.
Zhijin has not seen the Su Family
لم يرى تشيجين عائلة سو
for over ten years.
لأكثر من عشر سنوات.
How do you know all this?
كيف تعرف كل هذا؟
Zhijin told me herself.
أخبرتني Zhijin بنفسها.
No one from the Su Family has seen Zhijin in ten years.
لم يرى أحد من عائلة سو تشيجين منذ عشر سنوات.
So, who is Zhijin
إذن من هو تشيجين؟
is up to you.
الأمر متروك لك.
You're about the same age as Zhijin.
أنت في نفس عمر تشيجين تقريبًا.
As for looks,
أما بالنسبة للمظهر،
you do carry the grace of a refined young lady.
أنت تحملين نعمة سيدة شابة راقية.
Why don't you
لماذا لا تفعل ذلك؟
take Zhijin's place
خذ مكان Zhijin
and return to the Su Family?
والعودة إلى عائلة سو؟
This is extremely risky.
وهذا أمر محفوف بالمخاطر للغاية.
If caught, it could cost me my life.
إذا تم القبض عليه، فقد يكلفني حياتي.
I haven't lived long enough yet.
لم أعيش طويلاً بعد.
I dare not.
لا أجرؤ.
What?
ماذا؟
Don't you want to marry into Prince Zhenbei's Mansion
ألا تريد الزواج من قصر الأمير زينبي؟
to enjoy wealth and honor?
للتمتع بالثروة والشرف؟
Listen to you,
استمع اليك
who wouldn't want wealth and honor
من لا يريد الثروة والشرف؟
and have a life of luxury?
وتتمتع بحياة مترفة؟
Then go ahead.
ثم اذهب للأمام.
As long as I keep silent,
طالما أنني صامت،
the Su Family won't find out.
عائلة سو لن تكتشف الأمر.
From then on,
ومنذ ذلك الحين،
you will become a person above others.
سوف تصبح شخصًا فوق الآخرين.
You know far too much.
أنت تعرف الكثير جدًا.
If you don't go today,
إذا لم تذهب اليوم،
then death is your only option.
إذا كان الأمر كذلك، فإن الموت هو خيارك الوحيد.
Then,
ثم،
I'll give it a try.
سأحاول ذلك.
Don't forget who helped you along the way.
لا تنسى من ساعدك على طول الطريق.
Madam Yun, please rest assured.
السيدة يون، يرجى الاطمئنان.
If I truly marry into the Prince's Mansion,
إذا تزوجت حقا من قصر الأمير،
I will share wealth and honor with you.
سأشاركك الثروة والشرف.
You do have a conscience.
لديك ضمير.
Zhijin,
زيجين،
I will
أنا سوف
reclaim everything for you.
استعادة كل شيء بالنسبة لك.
Wanyan family,
عائلة وانيان،
it's time for you to repay what you owe me.
لقد حان الوقت لسداد ما تدين به لي.
My Lord,
سيدي
the bait has taken the hook.
لقد أخذ الطُعم الخطاف.
I'm being watched here.
أنا مراقب هنا.
What did the Master say?
ماذا قال المعلم؟
When will the items be moved?
متى سيتم نقل العناصر؟
The Master has given orders:
وقد أصدر السيد الأوامر:
do not act rashly.
لا تتصرف بتهور.
I'm just a simple woman.
أنا مجرد امرأة بسيطة.
I can't bear such a shock.
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل مثل هذه الصدمة.
Hmph.
همف.
Go back and tell the Master.
ارجع وأخبر المعلم.
That will cost extra.
وهذا سيكلف مبلغا إضافيا.
Additional payment is required.
يجب دفع مبلغ إضافي.
Take them down.
أسقطهم.
Speak.
يتكلم.
Where are they hidden?
أين هم مختبئون؟
I...
أنا...
I have no idea what you're talking about.
ليس لدي أي فكرة عما تتحدث عنه.
Who was behind that deadly agent?
من كان وراء هذا العميل القاتل؟
Deadly agent?
عميل قاتل؟
In our line of work,
في مجال عملنا،
we never ask guests' names.
نحن لا نسأل الضيوف عن أسمائهم أبدًا.
Very well.
جيد جدا.
I'd like to see whether it's your stubborn mouth
أود أن أرى ما إذا كان هذا فمك العنيد
or my tough methods that prevail.
أو أساليبي القاسية التي تسود.
Don't be so rough.
لا تكن قاسياً هكذا.
What if you accidentally kill her?
ماذا لو قتلتها بالخطأ؟
How about
ماذا عن
we play a game?
نحن نلعب لعبة؟
Everyone makes a cut on her.
الجميع يقومون بقطع عليها.
Let's see how long she can endure.
دعونا نرى كم من الوقت يمكنها أن تتحمل.
Sir...
سيد...
No, please.
لا من فضلك.
This man is truly ruthless.
هذا الرجل لا يرحم حقا.
Begin.
يبدأ.
Take this.
خذ هذا.
Sir...
سيد...
No.
لا.
You go ahead.
اذهب للأمام.
Sir,
سيد،
aren't you afraid of divine retribution
ألا تخاف من العقاب الإلهي؟
for forcing a confession through coercion?
لإجبار شخص على الاعتراف بالإكراه؟
Divine retribution?
الانتقام الإلهي؟
Keep going.
يستمر في التقدم.
Your turn.
دورك.
You.
أنت.
This man is so unpredictable.
هذا الرجل لا يمكن التنبؤ به.
He wouldn't remember me, would he?
إنه لن يتذكرني، أليس كذلك؟
Qianyue.
تشيانيو.
Qianyue, please save me.
تشيانيوي، من فضلك أنقذني.
Qianyue, help me.
تشيانيو، ساعدني.
Do you still want to return to the Su Mansion?
هل لا تزال ترغب في العودة إلى قصر سو؟
You
أنت
should go accompany Zhijin.
ينبغي لي أن أذهب وأرافق تشيجين.
Madam Yun.
Madam Yun.
How could you kill her?
كيف يمكنك قتلها؟
We haven't finished the interrogation yet.
لم ننتهي من الاستجواب بعد
It wasn't me.
لم أكن أنا.
How could I dare kill Madam Yun?
كيف يمكنني أن أجرؤ على قتل السيدة يون؟
You killed her.
لقد قتلتها.
Sir, you're mistaken.
سيدي، أنت مخطئ.
How could I ever dare kill Madam Yun?
كيف يمكنني أن أجرؤ على قتل السيدة يون؟
Didn't you say
ألم تقل؟
that we should each
أن كل واحد منا يجب أن
cut her once?
قطعها مرة واحدة؟
So many have already cut her before.
لقد قام العديد من الأشخاص بقصها من قبل.
I only gave her one cut.
لقد أعطيتها قطعًا واحدًا فقط.
I am innocent.
أنا بريء.
If you don't believe me,
إذا كنت لا تصدقني،
then take my worthless life.
ثم خذ حياتي التي لا قيمة لها.
Hmph, such a chance to avenge Zhijin.
همف، هذه فرصة رائعة للانتقام لتشيجين.
How could I let it slip away?
كيف يمكنني أن أتركه يفلت مني؟
He wanted to kill me.
لقد أراد قتلي.
You still don't believe me.
مازلت لا تصدقني.
I believe you.
واعتقد انكم.
But since she's dead,
ولكن بما أنها ماتت،
you can finish
يمكنك الانتهاء
what she hadn't finished saying.
ما لم تنتهي من قوله.
What does he want me to say? Could it be...
ماذا يريدني أن أقول؟ هل يمكن أن يكون...
[One day ago]
[منذ يوم واحد]
Sir, I think I know
سيدي، أعتقد أنني أعرف
where the place you are looking for is.
حيث المكان الذي تبحث عنه.
Lead the way.
قيادة الطريق.
I'm not sure if what I saw earlier
أنا لست متأكدًا مما رأيته في وقت سابق
is actually what they want.
وهذا ما يريدونه بالفعل.
Whatever.
أيا كان.
Just give it a try.
فقط جربه .
If you're lying to me,
إذا كنت تكذب علي،
you know what will happen.
أنت تعرف ماذا سيحدث.
No.
لا.
This path is uncertain.
هذا المسار غير مؤكد.
And his mood swings wildly.
ومزاجه يتقلب بشكل كبير.
I can't risk my life here.
لا أستطيع المخاطرة بحياتي هنا.
I need to find a way to escape.
أحتاج إلى إيجاد طريقة للهروب.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Since you've already found what you sought,
بما أنك قد وجدت بالفعل ما كنت تبحث عنه،
I will take my leave.
سوف آخذ إجازتي.
Mr Lord,
السيد اللورد،
although we found the firearms,
على الرغم من أننا وجدنا الأسلحة النارية،
we failed to capture the ringleader.
لقد فشلنا في القبض على زعيم العصابة.
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
This is enough for now.
هذا يكفي الآن.
What should we do about this Begonia House?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل بشأن بيت البيجونيا هذا؟
Let it be.
فليكن.
What did she call us here for?
لماذا اتصلت بنا هنا؟
What's going on here?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
These are our contracts.
هذه هي عقودنا.
Who is the person over there?
من هو الشخص هناك؟
The contracts and money are all here.
العقود والأموال كلها هنا.
From now on, you will all be free.
من الآن فصاعدا، سوف تكونون جميعا أحرارا.
Contracts?
العقود؟
Mine.
مِلكِي.
This is mine; that one's yours.
هذا لي، وهذا لك.
Yours is right here.
مكانك هنا.
Got it. We're free now.
فهمت. نحن أحرار الآن.
We're free.
نحن أحرار.
Thank you, miss.
شكرا لك يا آنسة.
What do you intend to do?
ماذا تنوي أن تفعل؟
[The Contract]
[العقد]
Didn't you hate me?
ألم تكرهني؟
You and I never had any grudge between us.
لم يكن بيننا أي ضغينة أبدًا.
Any grudges
أي ضغائن
have all been settled one by one.
وقد تم تسويتها كلها واحدة تلو الأخرى.
Aren't you leaving yet?
ألم تغادر بعد؟
[Signed by Qianyue]
[توقيع تشيانيوي]
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
Wen Yueqian is no more.
لم يعد ون يويه تشيان موجودًا.
In this world, there is only
في هذا العالم لا يوجد سوى
Su Qingran.
سو تشينغران.
♪In this world, who exactly♪
???في هذا العالم من بالضبط؟؟؟
♪Pushed me into the abyss?♪
???دفعني إلى الهاوية ؟؟؟؟
♪The sky is silent, and the sea says nothing♪
"السماء صامتة والبحر لا يقول شيئا"
♪Who shows me mercy in this world?♪
???من يرحمني في الدنيا؟؟؟؟
♪Cold winds sweep across the wasteland♪
???رياح باردة تكتسح الأرض القاحلة؟؟؟
♪Mercilessly gifting me snow and frost♪
???يمنحني الثلج والصقيع بلا رحمة؟؟؟
♪In this fleeting life♪
''في هذه الحياة العابرة''
♪No mercy, no answers♪
???لا رحمة، لا إجابات؟؟؟
♪Yet one lamp shines, unafraid to go out♪
ومع ذلك فإن مصباحًا واحدًا يضيء، ولا يخاف من الانطفاء؟؟؟
♪Time can twist, but people aren't perfect♪
???قد يتغير الزمن، لكن الناس ليسوا كاملين؟؟؟
♪Who decides who comes and who parts?♪
???من يقرر من يأتي ومن يفارق ؟؟؟؟
♪It all rests on a single hopeful thought♪
"كل هذا يعتمد على فكرة واحدة مفعمة بالأمل"
♪Why fear one last breath?♪
لماذا الخوف من النفس الأخير؟
♪Love is brief, full of regrets♪
???الحب قصير، مليء بالندم؟؟؟
♪I paint the sky as a fan♪
???أرسم السماء كمروحة؟؟؟
♪To blow away nightmares and scatter the dust♪
???لإزالة الكوابيس وتبديد الغبار؟؟؟
♪Can't resist the fate of being separated♪
???لا تستطيع مقاومة مصير الانفصال؟؟؟
♪By distance♪
???بالمسافة؟؟؟
[Exclusive content rights reserved]
[حقوق المحتوى الحصري محفوظة]
[by Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.]
[من قبل شركة يوكو لتكنولوجيا المعلومات (بكين) المحدودة]